(Leonard:)Or the police. Or Homeland Security.
So you're the reason...
(Penny:)...I have to walk up and down
three flights of stairs every day?
(Leonard:)So I did something stupid.
I'm sure you did stupid things.
(Leonard:)What were you doing seven years ago?
(Penny:)Excuse me, I was in high school.
Studying, keeping my nose clean...
(Penny:)...doing volunteer work
for the community.
(Past Penny:)Not pregnant. Yes!
Ha, ha!
Oh, Ubuntu, you are my favorite
Linux-based operating system.
(Past Leonard:)-Hey.
-Hello.
(Sheldon:)Why do I smell methacrylate?
Oh, clear nail polish. I had a mani-pedi.
(Leonard:)Men can get those.
(Leonard:)Anyway, I may owe you an apology.
(Sheldon:)There's doubt?
(Leonard:)I did agree to the thermostat setting
and I shouldn't have tried to change it.
(Sheldon:)That's not an apology.
That's simply an acknowledgment
that I was right.
(Leonard:)-Okay, I'm sorry.
-There you go.
(Leonard:)So we're good?
(Sheldon:)-Good what?
-Never mind.
(Leonard:)-Okay if I watch some TV?
-Go ahead.
MAN [ON TV]:
Up next: Babylon 5.
LEONARD: You're not even watching.
SHELDON: I can hear it.
LEONARD:
Oh, so the dialogue offends you?
SHELDON:
I would hardly call that dialogue.
LEONARD:
You are insane, you know that?
SHELDON: Don't make me turn that flag
upside down because you know I'll do it.